blackhillsenergy.com 2017-08-16

# Privacy Policy | Black Hills Energy

Black Hills Corporation, including its wholly owned affiliates and subsidiaries doing business as Black Hills Energy (collectively, “Black Hills Energy”) is sensitive to privacy issues concerning the use of information provided over the Internet. We understand the importance of protecting any personal information you may provide to us through the use of this website and the sub-sites for Black Hills Energy’s various business units (collectively, "this website").

You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to visit this website. To obtain information, services, or products via this website, or to allow Black Hills Energy to respond to your requests for information, you may be asked to voluntarily provide non-public, personal information. Examples of personal information might include your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number. We use your information to provide the information, products, or services you requested and to enhance your use of this website. We will only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy policies of the Black Hills Energy sub-sites.

We may provide your personal information to selected companies who perform marketing services on Black Hills Energy's behalf, or to other institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. Those agreements require that your personal information be used only to alert you to products or services that might interest you. We require our marketing partners to uphold our standards for protection of your personal information. If you wish to opt out of having your contact information shared with third parties, see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our web servers collect general information that does not relate to specific individual visitors, such as the number of visits to this website, the number of pages viewed, and the domains from which people visit this website. This information is evaluated and used to improve this website. As an added measure, we do not include personal or account information in non-secure e-mails that we send you via the Internet.

Black Hills Energy may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with the rights or property of Black Hills Energy or other users of the website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Black Hills Energy may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure.

This website contains energy-related information that may be educational to you. In addition, this website contains links to other sites not affiliated with Black Hills Energy. Your use of the non-Black Hills Energy websites is subject to the privacy policies of those sites. Black Hills Energy disclaims all responsibility for the privacy practices of non-Black Hills Energy websites.

Black Hills Energy may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy without notice. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy and our other policies on occasion to learn of any changes. By using this website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our websites. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept those changes. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, this website or your dealings with Black Hills Energy, you may contact us at the address given below.

### CHOICE/OPT-OUT AND CORRECTION/UPDATE OF DATA

To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of the following services: receiving communications from Black Hills Energy about new features or services, and transferring your personal information to third parties for the purpose of offering a product or service that we think would be of value to you. If you object to such use for any reason, you may stop that use by either:

  1. Sending an e-mail request to [customerservice@blackhillscorp.com](mailto:customerservice@blackhillscorp.com); or
  2. Sending a letter request by U.S. Mail to:

Black Hills Energy  
PO Box 6006  
Rapid City, SD 57709-6006

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request to the address above that credibly shows error. Please understand that in order to protect your privacy and security, we may also need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### SECURITY POLICY

Your payment and personal information is safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address so that it cannot be read over the internet.
